<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fan Li</title>
    <link>https://fanlidublin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fan Li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 19:39:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fanlidublin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of Text Analytics Module (COMP47600 in UCD)</title>
      <link>https://fanlidublin.github.io/post/text_analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanlidublin.github.io/post/text_analytics/</guid>
      <description>_ 1. Pre-processing: _
is about cleaning up text-data for future use, five typical steps including:
 &amp;ndash;Tokenization &amp;amp; Normalization &amp;ndash;Fix misspelling &amp;ndash;Stemming, lemmatization, pos-tagging &amp;ndash;Entity extraction &amp;ndash;Removing stop words  Tokenization : tokenization is a process to find boundaries between word-like entities in character string. Concretely, it helps to identify individual words, numbers, and other single coherent constructs. The nltk Python tokenizer works off a set of rules for handling things of different types, including rules are quite general (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics you need to know in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://fanlidublin.github.io/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 18:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanlidublin.github.io/post/test/</guid>
      <description>1. Eager vs Lazy Classiﬁers
Eager Learning Classiﬁcation Strategy
 Classiﬁer builds a full model during an initial training phase, to use later when new query examples arrive. More oﬄine setup work, less work at run-time. Generalise before seeing the query example.  Lazy Learning Classiﬁcation Strategy
 Classiﬁer keeps all the training examples for later use. Little work is done oﬄine, wait for new query examples. Focus on the local space around the examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recources</title>
      <link>https://fanlidublin.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 18:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanlidublin.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>These are my favorite resources you can use to grow yourself back up in machine learning, NLP, deep learning and other hot AI domains. All of the resources are available for free online. You can check them through the links respectively.
Machine Learning Theory  Machine Learning, Stanford University(Coursera) Machine Learning, Carnegie Mellon University Machine Learning, MIT Machine Learning, California Institute of Technology Machine Learning, Oxford University Machine Learning, Data School [Introduction to Machine Learning Course, Sargur Srihari])(http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>